Preliminary Guide to the Helen Coley Nauts Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Writings and Miscellaneous, Series VI
  - "William B. Coley, M.D.: His Life, His Mission, His Legacy" [unpublished biography of William Coley by Helen Coley Nauts; draft 1 of 2], 1997 May (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - "William B. Coley, M.D. Biography" [unpublished biography of William Coley by Helen Coley Nauts; draft 2 of 2], 1996 November (Box 117, Folder 2)